<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>YetAnotherTyler</title>
    
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	
    
      <item>
        <title>Curse of Strahd DM Diary - Session Six</title>
        <description>
          The Tome of Strahd - 
          The Burgomaster’s Mansion After having dealt with the druids at the Wizards of Wine in the last session, the party woke up at the Blue Water Inn. They had received some guidance from the Martikovs that Madam Eva’s fortune reading may be pointing them to the Burgomaster’s Mansion, so the...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-04-11-cos-diary-session-6/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-04-11-cos-diary-session-6/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Curse of Strahd DM Diary - Session Five</title>
        <description>
          The Town of Vallaki - 
          In The Shadow of Old Bonegrinder After facing off with the night hag Morgantha in the last session, the party was free to explore the Old Bonegrinder. Stepping through the front door, the ground floor was a complete mess, as Morgantha’s dretch minions had been busy preparing dream pastries. The...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-04-05-cos-diary-session-5/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-04-05-cos-diary-session-5/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Running Trollskull Manor's Grand Reopening</title>
        <description>
          
          As it is written, the reopening of Trollskull Manor in Waterdeep Dragon Heist is a bit lackluster, needing very little input from the players. Given the amount of time and gold needed to reopen the tavern, many parties (mine included) want to be involved in the establishment’s first day of...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-03-27-trollskull-skill-challenge/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-03-27-trollskull-skill-challenge/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Curse of Strahd DM Diary - Session Four</title>
        <description>
          Fourtunes of Ravenloft - 
          Meeting Madam Eva Having just arrived at the Tser Pool encampment at the end of the last session, the party waited to meet with Madam Eva. As they arrived towards the end of the day, they are told it might be best to introduce themselves in the morning. Instead, the...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-03-24-cos-diary-session-4/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-03-24-cos-diary-session-4/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Curse of Strahd DM Diary - Session Three</title>
        <description>
          Leaving the Village of Barovia - 
          Blood of the Vine After narrowly escaping The Death House in the last session, the party are invited for a drink at the village tavern by a young man named Ismark. On the way to the tavern, the party caught a delicious scent of meat and herbs, and spotted an...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-03-15-cos-diary-session-3/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-03-15-cos-diary-session-3/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Curse of Strahd DM Diary - Session Two</title>
        <description>
          Exploring The Death House - 
          Durst Manor After a brief encounter with Strahd in the last session, my players arrived in the Village of Barovia where they were led to a manor by two sobbing children. The children, Rose and Thorn, told the party that their baby brother was alone in the nursery upstairs. I...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-03-06-cos-diary-session-2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-03-06-cos-diary-session-2/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Curse of Strahd DM Diary - Session One</title>
        <description>
          Welcome to Barovia - 
          You Start in a Tavern! My journey as a Curse of Strahd DM began, as many great adventures do, in a tavern. Specifically, at The Lady’s Luck tavern in the town of Daggerford. I decided on using the Secrets of the Tarokka adventure hook by DragnaCarta, so my players all...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-02-25-cos-diary-session-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-02-25-cos-diary-session-1/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Creating a Vistana PC for Curse of Strahd</title>
        <description>
          
          During my Session Zero for Curse of Strahd one of my players told me they wanted to play as a fortune-teller. I felt this was a perfect opportunity to tie their character into the adventure by making them a Vistana, they agreed to my idea, so we set out to...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-02-21-creating-a-vistana-pc/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-02-21-creating-a-vistana-pc/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Waterdeep Dragon Heist: Final Thoughts</title>
        <description>
          
          Several months ago, I began my journey as a DM by running Waterdeep Dragon Heist for a group of friends, and last week we finished the adventure. I decided on WDH because I frequently saw it recommended for new DMs or players, and the story seemed straightforward but interesting. While...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-02-13-wdh-final-thoughts/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-02-13-wdh-final-thoughts/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Waterdeep Dragon Heist Recap: Chapter Four</title>
        <description>
          
          Now that my players completed their fireball investigation, and had their sights set on the Stone of Golorr, I was ready to start the final chapter of Waterdeep Dragon Heist. In Chapter Four, players should be chasing after the Stone of Golorr, hunting down the vault keys, and entering the...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-02-04-wdh-recap/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-02-04-wdh-recap/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WDH: Running Cassalanter Villa</title>
        <description>
          
          The villain’s lairs make up nearly half of the chapters in Waterdeep Dragon Heist, and they are sadly completely optional. When I ran the adventure, I knew that I wanted to have my players heist the lair of my selected villain, the Cassalanters. Having just ran the villa in my...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-01-31-wdh-cassalanter-villa/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-01-31-wdh-cassalanter-villa/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WDH: DMs Guild and Other Resources</title>
        <description>
          
          Waterdeep Dragon Heist has many resources from third parties to help expand on and better run the module, here are some of the ones that I found to be very useful. Sly Flourish: Session Zero Because WDH has a different style when compared to other prewritten adventures, I felt it...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-01-25-wdh-resources/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-01-25-wdh-resources/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Waterdeep Dragon Heist Recap: Chapter Three</title>
        <description>
          
          Chapter Three of Waterdeep Dragon Heist begins with a fireball going off in Trollskull Alley, the player’s main goal will be investigating what happened. My main concern with transitioning from the open-ended Chapter Two to the linear Chapter Three was motivating my players to get involved with the investigations, since...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-01-19-wdh-recap/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-01-19-wdh-recap/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cassalanter Asmodean Shrine Battlemaps</title>
        <description>
          
          These are some quick Dungeondraft battlemaps that I made for the Cassalanter Asmodean Shrine Outpost from The Alexandrian Remix. For these battlemaps the grid size is 256 pixels, feel free to use them as you please! In my campaign, I ran the Cassalanter outpost a bit differently than what was...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-01-16-cassalanter-outpost-maps/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-01-16-cassalanter-outpost-maps/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Waterdeep Dragon Heist Recap: Chapter Two</title>
        <description>
          
          Following Chapter One of Waterdeep Dragon Heist, my players had some treasure, and the keys to Trollskull Manor. My focus for Chapter Two of the module was renovating the manor, and completing some faction missions. Overall, we spent five sessions in this chapter, but the module is flexible enough that...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-01-13-wdh-recap/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-01-13-wdh-recap/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Waterdeep Dragon Heist Recap: Chapter One</title>
        <description>
          
          A few months ago, I began my journey as a DM by deciding to run the prewritten module Waterdeep Dragon Heist. As we now begin to wrap up the campaign, I wanted to start recapping my experience from each chapter in order to document my thoughts, and potentially give some...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-01-11-wdh-recap/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-01-11-wdh-recap/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
